I'll get coffee. Want anything, baby doll?
我要点咖啡外带 洋娃娃，你也要吗？
I'm fine. Thanks.
不用了，谢谢
I can't pull off "baby doll," can l?
我不能叫你洋娃娃吧
No,I think we learned that from the "sugar lips" incident.
对，从那次甜甜嘴事件 我们已经学到教训了
I'll make some tea.
我去点茶来喝
How you doing,pumpkin?
小亲亲，你好吗？
行不通
-So it's going well for you two? -I know. Really well.
你们俩看起来越来越好了呢 我知道，真的很好
I'm gonna ask Phoebe to move in with me.
其实我正想要菲比搬来我家
What do you think?
你觉得呢？
It's great! When will you ask her?
这真是太棒了 你何时要问她？
Tonight. But don't say anything.
今天晚上，你先别透露喔
I swear. I promise.
我发誓不说，人格担保…
I'm so excited!
天啊，我超兴奋的
But listen,do not get her flowers, okay?
我跟你说，记得不要送她花
Because she cries when they die. Then there's the whole funeral.
因为花谢了她会哭 还会帮花办葬礼之类的
-I'll see you after work,sweetie. -Okay. Bye.
亲爱的，下班后再见 好，再见
So, what movie should we see?
我们应该去看什么电影？
Gary's gonna ask you to move in with him!
盖瑞要请你搬去跟他住
What? Really?
什么？真的吗？
He made me promise not to tell, but I couldn't hold it in any longer!
他刚才在吧台上跟我说的 他要我保证不会说出去 但我实在是憋不住
I can't believe this.
我不敢相信
Right? Because it's fast. Because it's so fast. It's fast.
对，因为太快了，太快…
Relax. It's Phoebe, not you.
别激动，是菲比，又不是你
Good for you, Phoebe. Way to go.
菲比，很厉害，有一套
No, but it is fast, isn't it?
不过真的是很快，对吧？
-I like him, but I'm not ready. -So,what are you gonna do?
我是很喜欢他没错 但我还没有准备好要同居 那你打算怎么办？
I don't know. I'll just handle it. I'll ask you to talk to him!
不知道，兵来将挡 干脆找你去和他说！
Me? Why me?
我？为何是我？
Because you are so afraid of commitment.
因为你怕死了给承诺
You talk to him. Make him scared like you, make him a man.
你去跟他说说 让他跟你一样怕 让他成为一个…男人
I'll try, but I'm not sure what good it'd do.
我会去试试 但我不确定会多有用
I'm less afraid of commitment than I used to be.
因为比起以前 我现在已经不很害怕承诺了
That is so sweet.
真是太甜蜜了
Still terrified. I'll take care of it.
还是很怕 但我会处理，没问题
The One With the Ball
本集播出：“同居大不行”
rainystar压制iPod-MP4
Hey,Ross,is Staten lsland really an island?
罗斯，斯塔顿岛真的是岛吗？
That's why they call it Staten "lsland."
是啊，所以才叫斯塔顿“岛”
Oh,I thought it was like Long lsland.
我还以为那跟长岛一样
Also an island.
长岛也是岛
-What time is it? -2:17.
几点了？ 2点17分
We haven't dropped this ball for an hour.
你知道吗？我们丢这个球连续一小时都没有漏接落地
Are you serious?
你是认真的？
I realized it a half-hour ago, but I didn't say anything.
对，我半小时前就发现了 之所以没说
I didn't wanna jinx it.
是怕坏了好事
We are pretty good at this.
我们还真会丢接球呢
We totally forgot about lunch.
我们完全忘了吃午餐
That's the first time I've ever missed a meal.
这是我第一次忘记吃饭
I think my pants are a little loose.
对，我的裤子都有点松了
Hey,you guys. Is Monica here?
嗨，摩妮卡在吗？
I bought something. I'm not sure she'll like it.
我带了东西回来 我不确定她会喜欢
It may seem crazy, but I've wanted this since I was a little girl.
听起有点奇怪 那个东西我从小就想要了
You bought Shaun Cassidy!
你带的是史恩卡希迪？ （歌手）
No. I wish!
不是，我也希望是
Okay,you ready?
你们准备好了没？ 好了
那好
Check it out.
请看！
What is it?
那是啥啊？
What the hell is that?
什么鬼东西？
It's a cat.
这是猫啊
That is not a cat!
这才不是猫
Yes,it is!
这就是猫啊
Why is it inside out?
它的皮怎么翻出来了？
Excuse me!
帮帮忙
But this is a purebred, show-quality sphinx cat.
这可是展示级的 纯种狮身人面猫
How much did you pay for that?
你花了多少钱买的？
It was extravagant, but I got a good deal.
有点奢侈 但我谈到了很好的价钱
-How much? -Thousand bucks.
多少钱？ 一千美元
On a cat?
买一只猫？
It's not a cat!
那才不是猫！
For a thousand dollars, you'd think at least it'd come with hair.
花一千元起码也要有毛才对
Or something.
或是其他有的没的
All right. Listen, ball boys.
你们这两个玩球的给我听好
My grandma had one when I was little. It was the sweetest thing.
我小时候祖母就养了这种猫 它们最讨人喜欢了
It would sit in my lap and just purr all day long.
超可爱的，躺在我的膝盖上 整天满足地喵喵叫
I would drag a string and it would chase it.
我还会拿鞋带在地上拖 让它追着跑
Free cats do that too, you know.
不要钱的猫也会那样
It's not a cat!
那才不是猫！
I'm really excited about this,okay? I don't care what you think.
反正我买得很兴奋 我才不管你们怎么想
I'm gonna set up a litter box for Mrs. Whiskerson.
我要去帮威丝克森太太 张罗出一个小猫砂盒
What am I gonna call her? Fluffy?
不然我要叫它“毛毛”吗？
Do you wanna get something to eat, or see how long we can throw this ball?
你要去吃点东西吗？ 还是要看我们能来回丢多久？
The ball thing.
继续丢球 是喔
Wouldn't it be great if we could go for two hours without dropping it?
若我们连丢两小时不落地 那样是不是棒？
Yeah,it would!
对喔
Let's do it.
来吧 好
I have to pee.
我要尿尿
And Rachel's in the bathroom!
瑞秋却在洗手间里
Man,I didn't think we'd make it.
没想到这样也行
I know.
是啊
Don't switch hands, okay?
你别换手喔
Hey, ladies. What are you in here for?
小姐，你们在这里干嘛？
What are you doing here?
钱德，你来这里干嘛？
I am here to report a crime.
盖瑞，我是来报案的 是吗？
It's a crime that we don't spend time together.
我们俩不常聚在一起 是一种罪
What's up?
你有什么事？
You're thinking about moving in with Phoebe, and I thought we should talk.
听说你在考虑要菲比跟你同居 我心想我们或许应该聊聊
You know,man to...
男人…
...well,me.
跟我的对话
Sure,okay.
好啊，没问题
Are you crazy?
你在发什么神经？
Are you insane?
你疯了？
If you live with Phoebe,you two are gonna be living together.
若你和菲比同居 你们两个就会住在一起了
I considered that. It'd make me happy.
对，我考虑过了 我知道这会让我快乐
-You mean scared. -No,I mean happy.
你是说害怕吧 不，我是说快乐
Scared happy.
害怕？快乐？
What are you doing?
钱德，你在干嘛？
I'm trying to open your eyes!
我在让你张开眼睛啊 你看不出来吗？
If you live with Phoebe, she is always gonna be there.
若你和菲比同居 她就永远都会在
You get home,she's there. You go to bed, she's there.
你回家会看到她 你上床也会看到她
You wake up and, oh, yes, she's there.
你起床呢？对，她还是在
I know. I can't wait!
我知道，我都等不及了
Were your parents happy or something?
你父母的婚姻很幸福吧？
I was lucky enough to find someone that I really love.
钱德，我看这件事的角度是 我很幸运能找到我的真爱
I just want to be around her as much as I can.
我想要尽量多跟她在一起
When you say it, it doesn't sound so scary.
怪了，这件事从你嘴里说出来 感觉就没那么恐怖了
You know what I'm saying?
所以你懂我的意思吧？
Yeah,I think I do.
对，我想我懂
You know what?
这样吧
Move in with her. Move in right now. Maybe I'll move in with Monica.
跟她同居 马上就去跟她同居 或许我也应该和摩妮卡同居
No,it's too soon for you guys.
不成，你们不能操之过及
You're right about that.
是啊，你说的对
When they found the remains of the Mesozoic mastodon...
他们找到中生代乳齿象化石
...they discovered what appeared to be the remains...
却在嘴部发现到
...of a Paleozoic amphibian in its jaws.
类似古生代两栖类的构造
How did it get there?
怎么会牛头不对马嘴？
Maybe this should be more of a quiet game.
或许这个游戏应该安静一点
Hey,guys.
嗨 嗨
I left my watch here last night.
我昨晚把手表放在柜子上
-lt was here. Where is it? -I don't know.
本来还在这里，到哪儿去了？ 我不知道
I'm late for work.
别闹了，我上班快迟到了
How do you know? You don't have a watch.
你怎么知道？你又没戴表
Can you stop throwing the ball for one minute and help me find it?
能不能停一下再丢球 先帮我找表？
Oh, I don't know.... Yeah,can't do it.
不知道，没办法喔
-What? -Do not drop that ball.
怎样啦？怎样都好 千万别把球掉地上
We haven't dropped it in....
我们保持球不落地已经…
Two hours,27 minutes.
2小时27分钟
Really?
真的啊？
I won't make it in to work today.
我今天没办法去上班
I don't feel very good.
我人不太舒服
漂亮！
For a second, I thought I was feeling better, but I'm not.
我刚才突然觉得自己好多了 但其实没有
Hey, Rach.
瑞秋 嗨
Check it out. Almost three hours without dropping it.
快来看，球不落地接近三小时
Congratulations. That's quite a waste of time.
恭喜了，真是浪费时间
You have scratches all over you.
你身上都是抓痕，怎么了？
Well,it's my cat.
是我的猫
-Oh,I got a cat. -I don't want a cat!
对了，我养了一只猫 我不想养猫
Don't worry,it's not a cat.
别担心，那不是猫 没错
You guys,this cat is nothing like my grandmother's cat.
这只猫跟我祖母养过的猫 完全不一样
It's not sweet. It's not cute.
既不讨人喜欢，也不可爱
I dragged a string,and it flipped out and scratched the hell out of me.
我在地上拉着线逗它玩 它竟然发飙 把我抓得乱七八糟
I know this sounds crazy, but every time this cat hisses at me...
我知道这听来很疯狂 但我发誓 这只猫每次嘘我的时候
...I know it's saying,"Rachel!"
我知道它都在说“瑞秋”
Doesn't sound as crazy as paying $1000 for a cat.
花一千买美元买一只猫 比刚才那些话更疯狂
You paid $1000 for a cat when you owe me $300?
你欠我三百美元不还 还拿一千美元去买猫？
Well,I was gonna let you play with it.
我本来打算让你跟它玩的
“中央咖啡馆”
Did you talk to Gary about moving in?
你跟盖瑞聊过同居的事没？
I think you should do it.
聊过了，我觉得你应该答应
He's a great guy and he loves you a lot. You are a very lucky lady.
他很棒，他也很爱你 你非常幸运
You are useless!
你真没用
Freaking out about commitment is the one thing you can do...
害怕承诺是你唯一会做的事
...and you can't even do that right!
你竟然连那件事都做不好！ 天啊
Sorry. If he asked me, I'd move in with him.
抱歉 换做我都愿意和他同居
Get out of here,good-for-nothing.
窝囊废，你滚吧
Hey,Chandler.
钱德
Hey,Gar.
盖瑞
Hey,sweetie.
亲爱的
Can I talk to you for a second?
能不能先聊一下？ 好啊
You look pretty today.
你今天很美
Thanks. Okay.
谢谢，好吧
Here's the thing.
是这样的
I really want this relationship to move forward.
我很想让这段关系更进一步
If you're not moving forward, you're moving backwards.
因为不进则退
No, if you're not moving forward, you're staying still.
不对，那不是真的 如果不进，就是静止不动
And staying still is good. Watch this.
静止不动是很好的，你看
菲比 是
I want you to move in with me.
我要你搬来一起住
That is so sweet.
那真是太甜蜜了
But don't you think it's too soon?
但你不觉得太快了些吗？
There's so much we don't know about each other.
我们彼此还有太多地方不了解
Okay. I get it.
好吧，我懂了
I don't want us to jump into something that we're not ready for.
我只是不希望我们操之过急 你懂吧？
I don't want to mess up what we have.
我不想搞砸我们现在的一切
I'm worried it's gonna be a big mistake.
我担心同居会铸成大错
是啊
Which is why my answer is yes!
所以我的答案是我答应
Really?
真的吗？
You're so happy.
我好快乐
Monica, stop throwing it so hard!
摩妮卡，别丢那么大力！
We're on the same team!
我们是同一队
You guys have been doing this for four hours?
四个小时？ 你们就这样丢了四小时？
That's right,baby.
宝贝，没错
-All right. Let me in. -No,no! Don't do it!
好，让我加入 不行！…
What?
什么？
He's a dropper.
他是掉球大王
Oh,yeah. That's right!
对，没错！
I'm not a dropper!
我才不是掉球大王
It's really a three-person game, you know?
这其实是三个人的游戏
It's throwing and catching.
还不就是你丢我接
All right.
好吧
Oh,it's so hard.
好大力喔
Don't worry,guys. It's not a cat.
别紧张，那不是猫喔
Oh,good God!
我的…天啊
I give up. I don't know what I'm gonna do with this thing.
我放弃了 我不知道要怎么处理
Baking it didn't help?
送它进烤箱也没用？
Take it back to where you got it.
把它送回你买的地方呢？
I tried. They won't take her back.
我试过了，他们不收
Maybe that's because she's a minion of the Antichrist.
或许是因为它是反基督的爪牙
Why won't they take it?
瑞秋，店家为什么不收？
They said they would only give me store credit.
他们说要收回可以 但只退我店里的购物券
What am I gonna do? Get 1000 regular cats?
我要拿来买什么？ 一千只普通的猫不成？
You said it was a show cat. Why don't you show it,win some prize money.
你不是说这是展示猫吗？ 那就带去比赛拿奖品啊
Those shows cost a hundred bucks to enter, and all you win are these ribbons...
参加猫展要先缴一百美元 赢来的东西
...which technically belong to the damn cat.
还不是都归这死猫所有
You can keep it until you find out what to do with it.
不然你先留着罗 等到你找到处理的方法
That's not the point. I'm out $1000...
不行，那不是重点 我破费一千美元
...I'm all scratched up...
搞得全身都是抓痕
...and I'm stuck with this stupid cat that looks like a hand!
还跟长得像手的蠢猫困在一起
Oh,my God!
天啊
The cat's made my eyes water. Don't throw it to me!
那只猫害我流眼泪了 别丢球给我！
My vision's been compromised!
我的视力被连累到了
Oh,God! Okay.
天啊，好了…
It's okay. Man,that was close.
现在好了，真是惊险
Yeah,you almost overreacted to something.
是啊，你的反应也太大了点
-We have great news. -We're moving in together. Yay!
我们有个好消息 我们要同居了，是不是很棒？
Congratulations.
恭喜…
-I'm so excited! -So am l.
是啊 我好兴奋 我也是
You're not more excited than I am. No way. I'm the most excited.
你才没有我兴奋，不可能 我是最兴奋的
See you at the station later.
好，晚点在局里见
I'll see you later. Don't forget about the moving-in!
好，晚点见 别忘了同居的事喔
So you're moving in with him?
你要搬去跟他住，怎么了？
I couldn't tell him no. He got so sad. Maybe it'll be all right.
我不忍心拒绝他 看他伤心成那样 或许不会有事的
I do like him a lot...
我真的很喜欢他
...and probably do it eventually,anyway.
同居八成也是迟早的事
Plus,think of all the money I'll save on stamps.
想想也可以省下不少邮票钱
Do you write him a lot?
怎么着？你常写信给他？
I heard when people live together...
不是，只是我听说同居的人
...they split the cost of stamps,don't they?
会分担邮票的费用，不是吗？
-Yeah,yeah. -That's right.
是啊，没错…
Sorry,the oven mitts really freaked me out.
抱歉，耐热手套吓了我一跳
Hey,honey.
亲爱的
Did you find any apartments in Brooklyn Heights?
你找到公寓没？ 布鲁克林高地有吗？
No, nothing.
不，没找到
-Oh, really? -Yeah.
真的？ 是啊
-Nothing at all? -No.
一间都没有？ 没有
If something opens up,we'll move in. If it has a pool. I need a pool.
只要有公寓招租 我们马上搬进去 不过要有附泳池的 我需要泳池
Can I talk to you?
菲比，可以跟你聊一下吗？
Take a seat.
请坐 好
You okay?
你没事吧？
You feel all right?
还好吧？
I feel great, because we're moving in together.
我很好啊，因为我们要同居了
So you....
那么...
You checked the paper for listings in Brooklyn Heights,right?
报上布鲁克林高地的租屋广告 你都看过了？
You checked the Post?
邮报你有查过吗？
Yeah,there was nothing.
有啊，啥都没有
-Can I get some water? -ln a minute.
我能喝点水吗？ 等一下
You checked today's Post?
你查过今天的邮报吗？
Yeah,today's.
对，我是看今天的
Because this is today's Post.
这是今天的邮报
And these are the listings I found.
我找到了这些租屋广告
Brooklyn Heights, two bedrooms. Brooklyn Heights, one bedroom.
布鲁克林高地，两房 布鲁克林高地，一房
Brooklyn Heights,Brooklyn Heights, Brooklyn Heights!
布鲁克林高地地区…
Oh,are these for rent? I thought people were just bragging.
这些是要租的吗？我以为他们是在 炫耀自己的房子有多棒
Let me tell you what's going on here.
我来告诉你我的想法
Don't look at the table. Look at me.
不要看桌子，看着我
Somebody asked someone to move in with him.
一个男生要求一个女生同居
Someone said yes, but now she has doubts...
女生本来说好，现在反悔了
...because things are moving too fast. Does that sound possible?
因为女生觉得这样太快了 你觉得是不是这样？
Yes,fine! I am someone!
对！…好，我就是那个女生
You want me to say it? I have doubts!
你要我说老实话？ 对，我是不确定
I'm sorry!
对不起
菲比？
It's okay that you feel this way.
你有这种感觉也没关系
It is soon, and there's things we don't know about each other.
这真的是很快 我们对彼此有许多地方不了解
Everything I know about you, I really like.
我只是觉得 我知道的你，我都很喜欢
Things I don't know, I'll learn in a place with our names on the mailbox.
我还不知道的你 就等同居后再慢慢了解
That's so sweet.
那样好甜蜜喔
But if it's too soon for you, we don't have to do it.
不过如果你觉得这样太快 我刚才说的可以慢慢再来 不用赶着现在就同居
I want you to be happy.
我只想要你快乐
Living with you would make me happy.
跟你同居会让我快乐的
You don't have to say that.
菲比，你不用那样说
I want to live with you. I want to move in with you.
不，我很想跟你住在一起 我要跟你同居
Are you sure?
你确定？
Definitely,yes! Let's live in an apartment we both live in.
对，百分之百确定！ 我们一起住在公寓同居吧
Oh,that's great.
太好了
Oh,wait, one sec.
等等…
Hey,you! Behind the glass. Who are you looking at?
镜子后面的人 你看什么看！
I always wanted to say that every time I was in these rooms, which was never.
我每次进来这种房间 都想说这句话 虽然我从没进来过
Show cat!
展示猫
Quality show cat!
高级的展示猫
-Show cat! -Oh,my God!
展示猫 天啊
What's wrong with your baby?
你的宝宝怎么了？
That's not a baby. That's a cat.
这不是宝宝，这是猫
-It's creepy-looking. -Oh,no.
长得还真吓人 不
It's actually very sweet. It's very sweet. Look.
它其实很讨人喜欢的… 不信你看
Yeah. Do you want it?
你要不要？
No,I hate cats.
不了，我恨猫
Then what are you doing to me?
那你干嘛跟我扯半天？
Get out of here,all right? Move on!
滚吧，继续走你的路
What an unusual cat.
这只猫真不寻常
Yes,thank you! Exactly. You want it?
是的，谢谢你 真的是这样，你要吗?
Maybe.
有可能
I was thinking about getting a cat from the shelter,but....
我考虑要养猫 我正好要去流浪动物之家…
-Okay. Why not? -Oh,terrific! That'll be $2,000.
好吧，就它了 太好了，总共是两千美元
-What? -Okay,1000.
什么？ 好吧，一千
Didn't you want me to adopt your cat?
我以为你是要我认养你的猫
I do,but you'll have to look at this as more of an investment than a cat.
是啊，不过这不只是猫 更是一项投资
Okay,yeah. I just wanted a cat.
好吧，我要的只是猫
Obviously,you know how to haggle, so I won't try and take you on.
你显然是杀价高手 所以我就不唬弄你了
So $800,and I don't call the cops, because you are robbing me blind!
算你八百，我也不报警了 因为你这根本是抢劫
Blind! Just take the cat. Leave the money. Run away!
把钱留下，猫带走 溜之大吉吧…
Run away. Damn it!
快走吧 可恶！
Can't you at least smile or something?
死猫，你起码也笑一下嘛
Did anybody just hear that? Anybody?
有没有人听到？谁听到了？
-I'm starving. -Come on,guys. Suck it up!
我饿死了 你们振作一点
We're closing in on 10 hours.
就快达成连续十小时了
It's gut-check time!
这是比毅力的时刻
I don't know who made you the boss. We invented this game.
怎么变成是你当老大？ 这游戏是我们发明的
I made this game what it is!
帮帮忙，这游戏是因为我 才有现在的局面
Not fun anymore?
不再好玩的局面？
I'm still hungry.
我还是很饿
There's pizza at my place. We can eat with one hand. Are you with me?
好吧，我家还有一点比萨 你们可以用一手吃吧？ 要不要？
-I am. -All right,let's go! Come on!
我要 好，我们走…
Let's go, Team Monica!
摩妮卡大队，走罗
We can work out the name later.
好啦，队名等一下再讨论
What is your cat doing in my bowl?
瑞秋，你的猫在我碗里干嘛？
I'm defrosting a chicken.
不是啦，我在解冻鸡肉
I sold Mrs. Whiskerson.
我把威丝克森太太卖掉了
Thank God!
谢天谢地
-Get your money back? -Yeah,$1500.
你的钱拿回来没？ 有，一千五百美元
You made a profit?
哇，你还有赚耶
I just came for the red velvet pillow.
我是来拿红丝绒枕头的
-There you go. -Thanks,Rachel.
在这里 瑞秋，谢了
Don't forget, you can come visit her anytime.
别忘了，你随时可以来看它
Oh, good. Great. I'll keep that in mind.
好…我会记得的
So is this some kind of snake or something?
这是啥？某种蛇吗？
I like waking up with you.
我真喜欢和你一起醒来
I like waking up with you too.
我也是
Oh, it's such a beautiful morning.
今天早上真美
I could stay here all day.
我可以在床上待一整天
That would be great.
那样不错
-We could have breakfast in bed. -Wait,just a second.
我们可以在床上吃早餐 等等 好
Oh,no.
不会吧
All right. Come on, Monica! Look alive. Come on!
来，摩妮卡，活力点…
Oh,I was having the best dream.
我刚才做了最棒的梦
-What? -I dreamed I was drowning...
什么梦？ 我梦到自己溺水
...and not throwing this ball.
不用再丢这颗球了
Oh, good. You're all up.
很好，你们都起床了
It's 6:00 in the morning. Why aren't you at Gary's?
菲比，现在才早上六点 你怎么没在盖瑞那里？
-Oh, yeah. That's over. -What?
对，结束了 什么？
Gary's such a great guy. You can work it out.
别这样，盖瑞这么好 有什么问题都能解决的
-He shot a bird. -That is over.
他开枪杀了一只鸟 结束了
-I'm sorry. -That's terrible.
太糟糕了…我很遗撼…
Are you okay?
菲比，你还好吧？
I'll be all right.
对…我不会有事的
Here,Phoebe.
菲比，接住
I don't feel like playing.
我不太想玩球
It's okay. It's okay.
没事…
It didn't happen. No one needs to know.
就当没发生这件事 没必要让别人知道
She's not an official ball player.
菲比又不是正式的队员
Only official ball players can drop the ball.
正式队员掉球才算数
-Come on. -Let's go.
算了…我好饿…
You wanna get breakfast?
菲比，要吃早餐吗？
Okay, let's race!
好，我们来赛跑
First one there wins.
最先到的赢
You guys wanna eat here?
你们要在这里吃吗？
That was great,huh?
在这里就好
Can you believe how long we threw it?
真不敢相信我们丢了那么久
It is amazing it lasted that long.
是啊，撑了那么久 真的很不可思议
My arm is killing me.
是啊，我的手臂酸死了
No, I meant with the dropper over here.
不是，我是说有掉球高手在 还能那么久
How did I get this reputation as a dropper?
“掉球高手”这称号 怎么会落到我头上？
I am anything but a dropper.
我再怎么说也不是掉球高手
Ross!
罗斯…